prowrestling.com 2004-06-03

# ProWrestling.com - #1 Wrestling Website in the World!

**ProWrestling.com** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site, [**ProWrestling.com**](http://www.prowrestling.com/). Prowrestling.com is a web site for General Audiences, including adolescent, teen's or adults and no content will ever disclose any information or picture that is not appropriate for ALL audiences. However, our content is based around professional wrestling, and they sometimes create television angles that may not be appropriate for all audiences. Prowrestling.com will do its best to filter out this content at all time, rendering this site appropriate for ALL audiences. We urge you to beware of Chat rooms, Forums and/or any other device that allows fans to post their own comment because ProWrestling.com has no means of filtering out content of that nature. 

**_Advertisers_**   
_Third Party Advertising_  
We use MaxWorldwide and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp).

_Third Party Cookies_  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. 

**_External Links_**   
This site contains links to other sites. ProWrestling.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

**_Content_**   
Since ProWrestling.com is a public website, most of our content is submitted by our fans. ProWrestling.com takes every step possible to make sure that all content is suitable for all audiences. However, once in a while some material may be added to our site which shouldn't be here. If you find such material here, please notify us ASAP, and we'll be more than happy to remove it, usually within just a couple of hours. 

**_Public Forums_**   
At times this site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. In addition, Prowrestling.com will NOT be held responsible for ANY AND ALL content that is submitted by a fan. All of Prowrestling.com's message boards, fan forums, chat rooms are logged using IP tracking technology. If a user submits content that is not appropriate or might infringe on certain copyrights/trademarks, please contact the webmaster and additional information about that user will be provided if we see fit. 

**_Security_**   
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. e-Mail addresses are not stored on this webserver. 

**_Children's Guidelines_**   
We care about children and understand that they have special privacy needs. Therefore, we have adopted the following privacy policy regarding children: 

We will NOT collect, use, or distribute to third parties personally identifiable information without prior verifiable parental consent. 

We will NOT give the child access to unmonitored chat rooms, email accounts, or other services that would give the child the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable information without prior verifiable parental consent. When verifiable parental consent is not obtained, we will only use the online contact information (such as email) to: 

Respond directly to the child's request on a one-time basis and not use that information to re-contact the child for other purposes. 

Request the name or online contact information of a parent for the purpose of obtaining verifiable parental consent or providing parental notification. 

Respond more than once directly to a specific request from a child (such as in the case where a child requests a newsletter subscription) and not used to re-contact the child for other purposes. We will use our best efforts to provide parental notification, which will include the nature and intended use as well as an opportunity for the parent to prevent the use of the information and participation in the activity. 

We will NOT entice the child to divulge more information than is needed to participate in any activity, game, or service. 

We will provide the parent a description of the specific types of a personally identifiable information collected from their child upon request. We will allow the parent to refuse further use or future online collection of personally identifiable information and provide a way for a parent to obtain any personally identifiable information collected from their child. 

We will provide notice to children in age appropriate terms of what personally identifiable information is to be collected. 

We will NOT provide any links to Web sites that are unsuitable for children. 

We will encourage children to get their parent's permission before sharing personal information online. 

**_Contacting the Web Site_**   
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact the ProWrestling.com owner. 

**_Submit Notice_**   
By submitting any "Content" (information, forum posts, one-liners, links, feedback, content, etc) to ProWrestling.com or any ProWrestling.com staff member; you grant us a nonexclusive worldwide license to link to, reproduce, distribute, adapt, perform, display and sublicense the submitted Content. Further, by submitting Content to ProWrestling.com or any ProWrestling.com staff member, you acknowledge that you have the authority to grant us such rights. Please note that you retain ownership of any copyrights of all content you submit. If the submitted Content includes information or source code, which is in any way objectionable or harmful, our staff shall have the right to analyze, summarize, and report on this information as we see fit. Since this is a public website, most of our content was submitted to us by our users (forum posts, submitted one-liners, etc). Please notify us ASAP if you find any content on ProWrestling.com harmful and offensive and we'll be more than happy to remove it, usually within the next 3 business day. 

<< Go Back
